(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-31T21:18:40.628116",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
おはよう こんにちは こんばんは！
Good morning, good afternoon, good evening!
ERB TVの「Now That's a Bop」へようこそ！
Welcome to ERB TV's "Now That's a Bop"!
司会を務めるのは私... おーほっほっほ！
Hosting tonight is me... Ohohoho!
薔薇は紅く、我が心の炎は青く燃え上がる
Roses are red, the flame of my heart burns blue,
緋色の女王、そしてJusticeのリーダー！
the Scarlet Queen, and the leader of Justice!
エリザベス・ローズ・ブラッドフレームです！
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
Lovely to see you, to see you... Lovely!
会場には熱狂的なロザリアンの皆さんが集まっています！
The venue is packed with enthusiastic Rosarians!
最高の楽曲を届ける準備万端の素晴らしいクルーたちもね！ Huzzah!
And a wonderful crew ready to deliver the best tunes! Huzzah!
今夜は最高にノリの良い曲をたくさん用意しているわよ
We've prepared a lot of great bops for tonight!
今夜の特別なテーマは... 「80年代」！
Tonight's special theme is... the 80s!
お家で楽しんでいる皆さんも もし番組が気に入ったらハッシュタグで教えてね #ERBday2026 よ！ これ！これ！
Everyone enjoying at home, if you like the show, let us know using hashtag #ERBday2026! This one! This one!
OK! それでは最初の1曲目にいきましょう 準備はいい？ 「フライデイ・チャイナタウン」！
OK! Let's move on to our first song! Are you ready? "Friday Chinatown"!
It's so fly-day, flyday chinatown
真夜中の人混みに
In the midnight crowd,
It's so fly-day, flyday chinatown
はじけるネオンサイン
the neon signs pop.
肩にぶつかる外人
A foreigner bumps into my shoulder,
ウインクを投げる
and gives me a wink.
知らん顔の
You pretend not to notice...
知らん顔のあなた
Pretending not to notice, you...
とまどいのひとコマ
...a single scene of hesitation.
踊り疲れていても
Even if I'm tired of dancing,
朝まで遊ぶわ
I'll party until morning.
港の見える場所で
In a spot overlooking the harbor,
何か飲みたいのよ
I want to have a drink.
It's so Fly-Day, Fly-Day Chinatown
ジャスミンに接吻を
A kiss for the jasmine...
It's so Fly-Day, Fly-Day Chinatown
私も異国人ね
I'm a stranger here, too.
お店に並ぶ絹の
Pointing at the silk dresses...
ドレスを指さす
...lined up in the shop,
渋い顔のあなた
with your stern expression,
わがままが言いたい
I want to be a bit selfish.
愛想笑いのおばさん
The smiling lady says,
きっと似合うわと
"I'm sure it'll suit you!"
どこか静かな場所で
Somewhere quiet,
着替えてみたいのよ
I want to try it on.
It's so Fly-Day, Fly-Day Chinatown
絹擦れの月あかり
Moonlight rustling like silk...
It's so Fly-Day, Fly-Day Chinatown
私も異国人ね
I'm a stranger here, too.
It's so Fly-Day, Fly-Day Chinatown
ジャスミンに接吻を
A kiss for the jasmine...
It's so Fly-Day, Fly-Day Chinatown
私も異国人ね
I'm a stranger here, too.
男のコになりたい
I Want to Be a Boy
男のコになりたいのよ
I want to be a boy!
たしか
Surely,
星のハイウェイ バイク飛ばし
speeding down the starry highway on a bike,
あいつの後を 追っかけてゆくのさ
I'll go chasing right after him!
そして 夢を聞きたい
And I want to hear about his dreams.
今日一日だけでいい
Just for today is enough...
リボンをほどいて 男のコに させておいて
untie my ribbon and let me be a boy.
朝まで一緒で
Stay together until morning,
だけど Chance Chance いつか Chance Chance
but chance, chance, someday chance, chance,
ふたり Dance Dance するとき 君は ふいに 女に
when the two of us dance, dance, suddenly you'll...
戻るの
...turn back into a girl!
男のコになりたいのよ
I want to be a boy!
なぜか
Somehow,
世界中を 自由に旅したい
I want to travel freely all across the world!
バラを一輪 飾るスーツで
Dressed in a suit adorned with a single rose,
最後の夜を決めるの
I'll make our final night unforgettable!
今日一日だけでいい
Just for today is enough...
すべてを叶えて 女の子は 見せない
grant every wish, without showing the girl in me.
素顔が見たいの
I want to see your true face...
そして Chance Chance いつか Chance Chance
and chance, chance, someday chance, chance,
ふたり Dance Dance するとき 君は あいつ好みに
when the two of us dance, dance, you seem like you'll...
なりそう
...become just his type!
スウィート カップル P P U- P POP P P
Sweet Couple P P U- P POP P P
今日一日だけでいい
Just for today is fine,
リボンをほどいて
untie my ribbon
男のコにさせておいて
and let me be a boy.
朝まで一緒ね
We'll be together until morning,
だけど Jump Jump いつか Jump Jump
but Jump Jump, someday Jump Jump,
二人 Jump する時には ふいに女に戻るの
when we jump together, I'll suddenly turn back into a girl.
スウィート カップル P P U- P POP P P
Sweet Couple P P U- P POP P P
SWEET MEMORIES
[Title: SWEET MEMORIES]
Woo...
懐かしい
A nostalgic
痛みだわ
pain...
ずっと前に
I had forgotten it
忘れていた
a long time ago.
でもあなたを見たとき
But when I saw you,
時間だけ後戻りしたの
time turned back for a moment.
「幸せ？」と聞かないで
Don't ask, "Are you happy?"
嘘つくのは上手じゃない
I'm not good at lying.
友達ならいるけど
I have friends, but
あんなには燃えあがれなくて
I can't burn with passion like back then.
失った夢だけが
Why is it that only the lost dreams
美しく見えるのは何故かしら
look so beautiful to me?
過ぎ去った優しさも現在は
Even the past kindness is now
甘い記憶 Sweet memories
a sweet memory, sweet memories.
Don't kiss me baby, we can never be
So don't add more pain
Please don't hurt me again
I have spent so many nights
Thinking of you
Longing for your touch
あの頃は若すぎて
Back then, we were far too young,
いたずらに傷つけあった二人
hurting each other for no reason.
色褪せた哀しみも現在は
Even the faded sorrow is now
遠い記憶 Sweet memories
a distant memory, sweet memories.
Woo...
Na na na na na...
失った
Lost
夢だけが
dreams are all that
美しく...
look beautiful...
見えるのは 何故かしら
I wonder why I see it...
過ぎ去った 優しさも 今は
Even the kindness that has passed is now...
甘い 記憶 SWEET MEMORIES
...a sweet memory, SWEET MEMORIES.
You are watching ERB TV!
Brilliant!
Sora, that was a masterclass in elegance!
My heart is still melting! Doki-doki!
ありがとう！ Thank you! It was such a sweet time singing with everyone!
Thank you! Thank you! It was such a sweet time singing with everyone!
I get it, I get it! Sweet time, sweet memories. I see, I see, I see!
And the lovely Nerissa Ravencroft, you look absolutely smashing tonight!
Oh Liz, you're such a flatterer! I was watching from the wings, and I couldn't stop humming along!
Oh, I have a question for you guys! So if you two formed a unit, what would your name be? Something flashy for the 80s charts!
Um, well...
We have something in common, don't we? Blue...
And you're kind of legendary, I'm a demon... so me too, so...
How about BLUE MEGAMI-SAMA?
BLUE MEGAMI-SAMA!
Oh, I like that! I like that a lot! Wow, BLUE MEGAMI-SAMA!
Beautiful, so cool!
Sora, here's a question for you! We all know you are an idol, but tonight you look like a movie star! Which 80s movie would you want to star in?
Ah... E.T.!
E.T.! E.T.!
Oh, that's a good one, that's a good one! Yeah, yeah, yeah! I can buy a bike and you can hop in my bike, yeah!
Nerissa, question for you! You've got a powerful voice, yes! What is your favorite powerful band from the 80s?
I don't know if I'd call them powerful... You know the answer before I even say it: The Smiths!
Yes! I know you well enough that I already knew the answer! Yes, yes! But that's still a great answer, yes!
Okay, I'd better get off and get ready for the next wild track, yes, wild!
I'll leave you guys to it! Ta-ra, loves, ta-ra! Bye-bye!
You are watching ERB TV!
All right then, let's move on to the next song, darlings!
COBRA! Huzzah!
街を包む What's going on
Wrapping around the city, what's going on?
Midnight fog
孤独な シルエット 動き出せば
When the lonely silhouette starts to move,
それは 紛れもなく ヤツさ
That is unmistakably him...
コブラ Living in blue
Cobra, living in blue
コブラ Missing you true
Cobra, missing you true
COBRA... I'll meet you memories after you
背中に まとい付く 陰りは
The shadow clinging to my back
男という名の 物語
is a story of a man.
許されるはずもない PEACE AND LOVE
Forgiveness is forbidden, peace and love.
空をよぎる 危険なサイン
A dangerous sign crosses the sky.
抑えたバイオレンス くすぶった瞳
Suppressed violence, smoldering eyes.
一人 闇をあえぐ 奴さ
He's a guy struggling alone in the darkness.
COBRA Leaving you blue
COBRA Missing you true
COBRA I'll meet you memories after you
ハートに 刻まれた あの日は
That day engraved upon my heart...
ロマンと 呼ぶには 熱すぎて
...is far too passionate to simply call romance.
巡り来る 明日もない PEACE AND LOVE
There is no returning tomorrow... peace and love.
IT'S LOVE
[Song: IT'S LOVE]
周りにいつも男たち
There are always guys surrounding you,
とりまいてて なんだかまるで君は Venus
gathering around... you're almost like a Venus.
ついに起こった Miracle
A miracle has finally happened,
砂漠の中から見つけ出した Jewel
a jewel discovered in the middle of the desert.
迎えに行くよ どんな時も
I'll come to get you, no matter when,
振り回されても 絶賛 Crazy for you
even if you lead me on, I'm completely crazy for you.
形のみえない つながりを
An unseen connection...
信じたい IT'S LOVE
...I want to believe in it, it's love.
時には確かめ合いたいよ
Sometimes I want us to confirm it together.
DON'T YOU KNOW KNOW KNOW IT'S LOVE
小麦色した君の肌
Your wheat-tanned skin,
やたらソフトな ACTION 高すぎるよ TENSION
overly gentle actions, and through-the-roof tension!
会えない夜は目の下に
On nights we can't meet,
黒いアイシャドウを塗りにおいで
come overlay dark eyeshadow beneath your eyes.
違う匂いじゃ気がつかない
If it's a different scent, I won't notice.
スタイル通りまとまって Must be you
Composed in your own style, it must be you.
形のみえない つながりで
Through an unseen connection...
感じたい HEART TO HEART
...I want to feel it, heart to heart.
時には確かめ合わなくちゃ
Sometimes we have to confirm it with each other.
DON'T YOU KNOW KNOW KNOW IT'S LOVE
飾らない素顔に戻るとき
When you return to your unadorned, natural face,
容赦なく涙も見せてくれただけに
just because you showed me your tears without holding back...
離さない 離れない このままいつまでも
I won't let go, we won't part, like this forever.
時を重ねていこう そしていつか COME TOGETHER
Let's stack time together, and someday come together.
形のみえない つながりを
An unseen connection...
信じたい IT'S LOVE
...I want to believe in it, it's love.
時には確かめ合いたい
Sometimes I want us to confirm it together.
No, don't you know, know, know
形の見えない 繋がりで 感じたい
I want to feel a connection that can't be seen...
Heart to heart
ときめきを確かめあわなくちゃ
We have to make sure of this excitement,
Don't you know, know, know, it's love
You are watching ERB TV!
もしも願いが 叶うなら
If my wish could come true,
吐息を白い バラに変えて
I'd turn my sighs into white roses.
逢えない日には 部屋じゅうに 飾りましょう
On days we can't meet, I'd decorate my whole room with them,
貴方を想いながら
while thinking of you.
Darling, I want you 逢いたくて
Darling, I want you, I miss you so.
ときめく恋に 駆け出しそうなの
I feel like running into a heart-fluttering love.
迷子のように 立ちすくむ わたしをすぐに 届けたくて
Standing frozen like a lost child, I want to reach you right away.
ダイヤル回して 手を止めた
I dialed your number, then stopped my hand.
I'm just a woman Fall in love
If my wishes can be true
Will you change my sighs to roses, whiter roses Decorate them for you
Thinkin' 'bout you every night And find out where I am
I am not Livin' in your heart
I am not living in your heart.
Darling, I need you どうしても
Darling, I need you, no matter what.
口に出せない 願いがあるのよ
I have a wish I just can't say aloud:
土曜の夜と 日曜の
On Saturday night and Sunday,
貴方がいつも 欲しいから
I always want you by my side.
ダイヤル回して 手を止めた
I dialed your number, then stopped my hand.
I'm just a woman Fall in love
Darling, you love me 今すぐに
Darling, you love me, right this instant
貴方の声が 聞きたくなるのよ
I want to hear your voice so badly.
両手で 頬を 押さえても
Even if I hold my cheeks in both hands,
途方に暮れる 夜が嫌い
I hate these nights where I feel so helpless.
ダイヤル回して 手を止めた
I dialed your number, then stopped my hand.
I'm just a woman Fall in love
Don't you remember When you were here
Without a thinking We were caught in fire
I've got a love song But where it goes
Three loving hearts are pulling apart of one
Can't stop you, can't hold you, can't wait no more
I'm just a woman fall in love
Love...
青い水平線を
The blue horizon
いま駆け抜けてく
Running through right now
とぎすまされた
Feeling the sharpened...
時の流れ感じて
...flow of time
ときめきへと
Towards excitement,
動き出す世界は
the world that starts to move...
忘れかけてた 遠い夢の訪れ
...is the arrival of a distant dream I had almost forgotten
Ride on time さまよう想いなら
Ride on time, if your feelings are wandering
やさしく受け止めて そっと包んで
Gently accept them, softly embrace them
Ride on time 心に火を点けて
Ride on time, light a fire in your heart
あふれる喜びに 拡がれ Ride on time
Spread into the overflowing joy, Ride on time
僕の輝く未来
My shining future
さあ回り始めて
Come on, start turning
うつろな日々も 全て愛に溶け込む
Even the hollow days all melt into love
なんという朝
What a morning
いますぐ君のもと
Right now to your side
届けに行こう
Let me go deliver to you
燃える心
A burning heart
迷わず
Without hesitation
Ride on time 時よ走り出せ
Ride on time, time, start running!
愛よ光り出せ 目もくらむほど
Love, start shining, so brightly it's blinding!
Ride on time 心に火を点けて
Ride on time, light a fire in your heart
飛び立つ魂に 送るよ Ride on time
I send this to your soaring soul, Ride on time
届けに行こう
Let me go deliver to you
燃える心
A burning heart
いまこそ
Right now!
Ride on time 時よ走り出せ
Ride on time, time, start running!
愛よ光り出せ 目もくらむほど
Love, start shining, so brightly it's blinding!
Ride on time 心に火を点けて
Ride on time, light a fire in your heart
飛び立つ魂に 送るよ Ride on time
I send this to your soaring soul, Ride on time
Ride on time さまよう想いなら
Ride on time, if your feelings are wandering
やさしく受け止めて そっと包んで
Gently accept them, softly embrace them
Ride on time 時よ走り出せ
Ride on time, time, start running!
青い水平線を
Cutting across the blue horizon,
いま切る RIDE ON TIME
right now, ride on time.
RIDE ON TIME 心に火を点けて
Ride on time, light a fire in your heart,
走り出す 愛の力で
start running with the power of love.
RIDE ON TIME 目もくらむほど
Ride on time, so bright it's blinding.
RIDE ON TIME 心に火を点けて
Ride on time, light a fire in your heart.
さまよう心に おくるよ RIDE ON TIME
Sending this to your wandering heart, ride on time.
You're watching ERB TV!
I don't know how to dance...
Unbelievable! Are we in a 1980s high school disco?
Oh, disco, disco! Yeah, disco!
Does this uniform suit me?
Ooh, it's super cute! You both look kawaii!
But the real question is, is the world ready for such charm?
You've captured the very heart of everyone watching, including mine!
Thank you!
Liz, is this mustache real?
Hey, hey, hey! Hands off, hands off, hands off!
This here is top-tier Exordian craftsmanship!
But I mustache you a question!
Anyway, Korone! I heard you're a tough pooch.
Between you and Marine, who would be the leader of the school?
じゃあ、ころね！かかってこい！
Well then, Korone! Bring it on!
Okay, Marine! Come on!
Break it off, break it off! No, no, break it off, break it off!
This is the '80s, ladies! This is the '80s!
We settle things with a dance-off!
Which leads me to my next question...
Who would win in a dance battle?
お前もかよ！
You too?!
Anyway, I'd love to stay and chat, but I've got to dash!
Korone, Marine, please lead us into the next song!
Cheers, ladies! Let's go!
Okay! Okay! 次の曲は何かな？
Okay! Okay! What's the next song?
エネルギッシュな曲と聞いてますよ！
I heard it's a super energetic song!
よし、準備はいいみたいだね！
Alright, looks like everything's ready!
せーの！オラに元気を分けてくれ！ Huzzah!
Ready, set, go! Lend me your energy! Huzzah!
光る 雲を突き抜け FLY AWAY (FLY AWAY)
Piercing through the shining clouds, I fly away (fly away)!
からだじゅうに 広がるパノラマ
A panorama spreads throughout my body!
顔を蹴られた地球が怒って (怒って)
Kicked in the face, the Earth gets angry (gets angry),
火山を爆発させる
making a volcano explode!
溶けた北極の中に
Within the melted Arctic ice,
恐竜がいたら 玉乗り仕込みたいね
if there's a dinosaur, I want to teach it ball-balancing!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
何が起きても気分は へへのへのカッパ
No matter what happens, it's a piece of cake!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
胸がパチパチするほど 騒ぐ元気玉... SPARKING!
My heart crackles with excitement, a roaring Genki-Dama... SPARKING!
騒ぐ元気玉...
The Genki-Dama roars...
Sparking!
空を急降下 Jet coaster
Diving through the sky on a roller coaster,
落ちてゆくよ パニックの楽園へ
I fall into a paradise of panic!
景色 逆さになると 愉快さ
The scenery turns upside-down and I cheer up,
山さえ お尻に見える
'cause the mountains even look like butts!
悩む時間はないよ
There's no time for worrying,
どこかに潜む「ビックリ!」に逢いたいから
'cause there's a surprise hidden somewhere, and I wanna find it!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
頭カラッポの方が 夢詰め込める
I'd rather have my head be empty, so I can stuff it with dreams!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
笑顔ウルトラZで
With a smile that's Ultra-Z,
今日もアイアイアイアイアイ
even today is Ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
何が起きても気分は へへのへカッパ
No matter what happens, I feel like it's no big deal!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
胸がパチパチするほど
Just as loudly as my heart pounds,
騒ぐ元気玉...
the Genki-Dama roars...
Sparking!
You are watching ERB TV!
Absolutely bonkers! Standing ovation!
And a round of applause for that spectacular energy! We did it!
Welcome to the MC desk, Nene and Iroha!
Yeah!
リズ、お誕生日おめでとう！
Liz, happy birthday!
Oh, yes! It's my birthday!
Happy birthday! Happy birthday to you! あ、ありがとう！ありがとう！
Happy birthday! Happy birthday to you! Oh, thank you! Thank you!
リズ、とってもパワフルだね！
Liz, you're so powerful!
Powerful dance! Powerful singing! And powerful pose!
Powerful dance! Powerful singing! And a powerful pose!
Oh, yeah, yes! Very powerful poses.
そんでもってキュート！
And super cute!
ねね、ソーキュート。リズ、ラブ！ I love you too!
Nene, so cute! Liz, love! I love you too!
ずるい！来ないで！ラブ！ I love you too!
Not fair! Don't come near! Love! I love you too!
I love you too! Thank you! We're very powerful!
So you're very powerful! Everyone was so powerful!
みんなブロンドヘア（金髪）だね！
Everyone turned into blonde hair, right?
Yeah, yeah! Blonde hair is super powerful! 超サイヤ人！
Yeah, yeah! Blonde hair is super powerful! Super Saiyan!
Super Saiyan blonde hair, you know? Very powerful! The strongest!
Yes! And I felt everyone's power.
And Nene, your energy is like a dragon!
Could you show the viewers your most powerful dragon pose?
ドラゴンポーズ！
Dragon pose!
ガオーッ！
Roar!
ドラゴンマウス！
Dragon Mouth!
ガッチンガッチン！
Chomp, chomp!
かっこいい！強そう！すごい！
So cool! Looks so strong! Amazing!
Wow, that was incredible!
And Iroha, your focus during that dance was amazing!
Could you demonstrate your finest samurai warrior stance?
OK 見てて！拙者はサムライだよ！
Okay, look! I am a samurai!
ズン... ズズン... シュッ... スゥー...
Dun... dudun... swish... sss...
ジャキーン！
Schwing!
A strong, strong samurai warrior! 強い！強い侍だね！
A strong, strong samurai warrior! Strong! A strong samurai!
You both performed in a big group tonight, there were seven of us all together on stage!
Tell me, who was the most CHA-LA, carefree member at rehearsals?
Are you pointing to Nene?
リハーサル中もずっとそうだったよね！
She was like that during rehearsal the whole time too!
Congratulations!
みんなで やろう みんなで
Let's do it together, everyone!
みんなでやろうよ！
Let's all do it together!
せーの！ Congratulations! Standing ovation!
Ready, set... Congratulations! Standing ovation!
ねね先輩が一番チャラいわ！ チャラチャラ！
Nene-senpai is the most playful! Chara-chara!
キュートでチャラい！最高だわ！ チャラチャラ！
Cute and playful! The best! Chara-chara!
What a marvelous time we had! Yes!
But sadly, it's come to our last two minutes! I must prepare for the Grand Finale! I shall return very soon, gang!
Nene, Iroha, please keep the audience entertained for a moment!
Okay? All right, warriors, see you soon!
バイバイ！頑張って！
Bye-bye! Good luck!
さあ、今夜のスターのリズは一体最後に何を見せてくれるでしょうか！
Now, what kind of final performance will tonight's star, Liz, show us?
ね、楽しみですね！じゃあ皆さん、観るのそのままで！それでは、行きましょう！
We're so excited! Everyone, stay tuned and enjoy the show! Here we go!
You are watching ERB TV!
せーの、ハッザー！
Ready, set... Huzzah!
I believe the morning sun always gonna shine again and
I believe a pot of gold waits at every rainbow's end, oh
I believe in roses kissed with dew, why shouldn't I believe the same in you?
I believe in make-believe, fairy tales and lucky charms and
I believe in promises spoken as you cross your heart, oh
I believe in skies forever blue, why shouldn't I believe the same in you?
You may say I'm a fool, feeling the way that I do
You can call me Pollyanna, say I'm crazy as a loon
I believe in silver linings and that's why I believe in you
I believe there'll come a day, maybe it will be tomorrow
When the bluebird flies away, all we have to do is follow
I believe a dream can still come true, why shouldn't I believe the same in you?
You may say I'm a fool, feeling the way that I do
I believe in friends and laughter and the wonders love can do
I believe in songs and magic and that's why I believe in you
You may say I'm a fool, feeling this way about you
There's not much I can do, I'm gonna be this way my life through
'Cause I still believe in miracles, I swear I've seen a few
And the time will surely come when you can see my point of view
I believe in second chances and that's why I believe in you
Hello, sweethearts!
Lovely to see you, to see you... Lovely!
What did you think of the first show on ERB TV?
Did you enjoy it? What did you think of the song choices?
I really hope you loved it as much as I loved performing with such amazing guests.
Huzzah!
Rosarians, to arms!
Are you ready for the surprise?
I have something lovely to present to all of you!
Here we go... 3, 2, 1!
I have birthday merch!
First up is this!
The beautiful key visual art of this birthday merch is on a tapestry!
I'm relaxing with Bobby and a cute Rosarian after a dance workout.
Please display this wonderful retro-style tapestry and take pictures for me to see, please!
Would absolutely love to see how you decorate the room with it.
As you've visited the TV studio, make sure to pick up your very own ERB TV mug!
Use it to hydrate while watching me on the telly!
"Mum, I'm on ERB TV!" "Hey Mum, I'm on the telly!"
I go saying that and most likely right now Queen Mother is watching this on the telly!
Next, you've all been wanting this, and so have I! A Rosarian plushie!
Aah! I'm so freaking happy!
My adventures have been nothing without my loyal, amazing Rosarians.
Now you can have your very own Rosarian, Bloodflame Kingdom powerful pooch!
I am your sword and you are my shield. We are powerful together!
That's right!
Next, we have a set of 4 pin badges!
You all know I love collecting pin badges, and here's some new ones for you to collect!
We have the ERB TV logo badge, shield badge, Rosarian paw,
and a Rosarian with a headband on saying BFK.
Bloodflame Kingdom represent!
You all look amazing with an 80s headband on, I must say!
Lastly, I recorded another voice pack in both English and Japanese!
The voice pack is called "Exercise with Elizabeth".
So join me on our training arc as we exercise together!
Onwards and upwards!
Then, if you purchase the whole set, the full shebang,
there's a full set purchase bonus!
You get a postcard with the key visual on it, but that's not all!
The limited quantity includes
a postcard with a handwritten signature by yours truly!
Please do not worry! Even when those run out, you still get the postcard with my replica signature!
And that is the full set of my birthday merch!
What do you think?
There's been a lot of love put into this merch,
and I especially can't wait to cuddle my own Rosarian plushie!
Wow. Before we wrap up, I'd like to give a special thanks to the guests.
It is an honor performing with you all. I'll treasure these sweet memories forever.
Thank you to the crew. Amazing job, everyone!
Thank you to my dance teachers who made the choreos.
I hope it made you proud with my moving and grooving!
Most of all, thank you, my beautiful kingdom, my Rosarians,
for checking out my first birthday live!
First ERB TV show!
Those were some bops and a half, right?
Okay, make sure to eat good noms, hydrate, get good sleep,
because we want our kingdom to be good and strong!
I love you all very much!
And most of all, let my voice be your strength!
Mwah! Bye-bye~
You're watching ERB TV!
イェイ イェイ イェイ イェイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
インドア系 (ハイ！) インドア系 (ハイ！) インドア系インフルエンサー
Indoor-type (Hey!) Indoor-type (Hey!) Indoor-type influencer
ベッドの上で 世界を廻せ
Turn the world around from on top of my bed
パジャマのままで バズらせろ
Go viral while still in my pajamas
カーテン閉めて 準備はOK
Close the curtains, setup is complete
光る画面が わたしのステージ
This glowing screen is my stage
TLを泳ぐ 流行の波
Riding the wave of trends through the TL
バズりのレシピ？ 教えない秘密！
The recipe for going viral? That's my secret!
通知の音で 目が覚める朝
Waking up in the morning to notification sounds
今日も今日とて オンライン
Today, as always, staying online
外の天気なんて 知らなくていい
I don't need to know what the weather's like outside
ここがわたしの 理想郷
Right here is my utopia
指先ひとつで 繋がる世界
A world connected with just a single fingertip
広がる無限の ストーリー
An infinite story expanding before us
だれかの「いいね！」が 欲しくって
Craving someone's "Like"
夜更かししちゃうの 毎晩ね
I end up staying up late every single night
だけど後悔なんて してないよ
But I don't regret it for a second
だってわたしは…
Because after all, I am...
インドア系インフルエンサー
Indoor-type influencer
部屋の隅から 発信中！
Broadcasting live from the corner of my room!
キミのハートに トレンド旋風
Sweeping your heart with a whirlwind trend
届いてるかな？ この想い
Are these feelings reaching you?
インドア系インフルエンサー
Indoor-type influencer
画面越しでも 伝えたい！
Even through a screen, I want to tell you!
引きこもりだって 夢がある
Even a shut-in has big dreams
世界を染めてく My Style
Painting the world in My Style
インドア系 (ハイ！) インドア系 (ハイ！)
Indoor-type (Hey!) Indoor-type (Hey!)
インドア系インフルエンサー
Indoor-type influencer
インドア系 (ハイ！) インドア系 (ハイ！)
Indoor-type (Hey!) Indoor-type (Hey!)
インドア系インフルエンサー
Indoor-type influencer
イェイ！ イェイ！ イェイ！ イェイ！
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
ずっとずっと 部屋のなか
Always and forever, inside my room
キミとつながる 居場所だよ
This is the place where I connect with you